

### Personal details



Eduardo Salazar



e.salazar.v.252@gmail.com



+58 424 135 55 01



Caracas - Venezuela



linkedin.com/in/ eduardosalazar-3a92791bb

### Skills

Visual Studio	••••
SQL Server Manager	••••
IIS Manager Studio	••••
Azure DevOps	••••
Trello	••••
ASP.NET Framework	••••
MVC	
ASP.NET Core MVC	••••
ASP.NET Blazor	••••
HTML5/CSS3/	••••
JavaScript	
C#	••••
MSSQL	••••
GitHub	••••
Microsoft Office	••••

# Languages

Spanish	••••
French	••••
English	••••

# Eduardo Salazar

Full Stack Developer

## Profile

Experienced Full Stack skilled in W.I.S.A. web solution stack (Windows Server, Internet Information Services, Microsoft SQL Server and ASP.NET), Blazor framework and various development languages. Currently working as a self-motivated Full Stack Developer focused on project execution. Self-directed learning and software development are my passion.

# **Employment**

#### **Analyst Semi-Senior**

Sep 2021 - Present

Ostos, Velázquez & Asociados - KPMG, Caracas - Venezuela

- Create new digital products.
- Transform, adapt and bringing routines or working methodologies to the digital world.
- Applying the Scrum framework on a day to day basis.
- Designing and developing Web Applications in an ASP.NET Blazor.
- Re-engineering projects from (Framework) MVC model and Core MVC model to ASP.NET Blazor.
- Front-End development with: CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript.
- Back-End development with: C#.
- Services: Claim Transformations, Active Directory, Email Service, Fluent Validations and more.
- Using SQL management studio to create relational database for projects.
- Create and set up Microsoft web servers.
- Create and set up Applications Pools and Sites using IIS server manager to publish projects in DEV and PROD environments.
- Train and manage junior responsibilities.
- Identifying training needs.
- Helping juniors in career development.
- Tracking training and development progress.
- Give support through Service Desk for several internal applications.

#### Consultant 1

Sep 2019 - Sep 2021

Ostos, Velázquez & Asociados - KPMG, Caracas - Venezuela

- Create new digital products.
- Propose and develop digital solutions to customer problems.
- Transform, adapt and bringing routines or working methodologies to the digital world.
- Applying the Scrum framework on a day to day basis.
- Designing and developing Web Applications in an ASP.NET (Framework) MVC model.
- Designing and developing Web Applications in an ASP.NET Core MVC model.
- Front-End development with: CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript.
- Back-End development with: C#.
- Services: Claim Transformations, Active Directory.
- Using SQL management studio to create relational database for projects.
- Give support through Service Desk for several internal applications.

## Hobbies

- Climbing
- Play Bass Guitar
- Reading
- Learning

#### **Mathematics Tutor**

Self-employed, Caracas - Venezuela

- Facilitated several math courses as an assistant by offering additional guidance and support to struggling students during class.
- Completed comprehensive performance review sessions, contributing to a 40% increase in students' grades.

Jan 2014 - Aug 2019

- Specialized as an individual tutor by simplifying math concepts and coaching students to develop problem-solving and critical-thinking skills.
- Tracked students' progress and identified alternative tutoring strategies to help students achieve their math goals.
- Improved students' algebra skills significantly by creating practice quizzes and worksheets to help prepare for tests and exams.
- Developed daily lesson plans for activities which helped cultivate a positive, fun, and engaging learning environment for students.

Multipurpose worker
SARL SBSE- Speed Burger, Saint-Étienne - France

Multipurpose worker
Sep 2013 - Jun 2016
May 2013 - Sep 2013

AVB Services SARL- Domino's Pizza, Lyon - France

Multipurpose worker May 2012 - Aug 2012

AVB Services SARL- Domino's Pizza, Lyon - France

### Education

# Agile Management with Scrum Aug 2020

Sybven, Caracas - Venezuela

# Computer sciences Sep 2016 - Aug 2019

Universidad Central de Venezuela, Caracas - Venezuela

Industrial Design Sep 2013 - Sep 2014

EDAA, Saint-Étienne - France

Bank, Law and Economy Sep 2012 - Aug 2013

IFC, Saint-Étienne - France

Civil Engineering & Mechanical Sep 2010 - Aug 2012

**Engineering** 

Université Claude Bernard (Lyon I), Lyon -

France

Physics, Chemistry Engineering Science Sep 2008 - Aug 2010

Université Claude Bernard (Lyon I), Lyon -

France

Scientific Baccalauréat Title Sep 2007 - Jun 2008

Colegion Francia, Caracas - Venezuela